jafx.com 2017-01-21

# Privacy Policy | JAFX

Privacy Policy  
It is our policy to respect the confidentiality of information and the privacy of individuals. We are also bound by principles contained in the Data Protection Act 1998 and the EU e-Privacy Directive.

This Policy will be reviewed from time to time to take account of changes to our operations or practices and, further, to make sure it remains appropriate to any changes in law, technology and the business environment. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. Any information held will be governed by our most current Policy.

INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU

We may collect and process the following data about you:

Information that you provide by filling in forms on our website www.jafx.com. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our website, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our website.  
If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence  
We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them  
Details of transactions you carry out through our website  
Your historic trading track-record, and information about any trades from the point you start reporting them to us  
Details of your visits to our Website including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access  
Your contributions to us and/or to the website.  
IP ADDRESSES

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

HOW WE USE COOKIES

Our Website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our Website. For further information, please see our Cookie Policy.

WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA

All information you provide to us is stored on secure servers within the European Economic Area, or with providers that comply with the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework, as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password, which enables you to access certain parts of our website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

The privacy and confidentiality of your personal information is of fundamental importance to us. We take all appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorised access to or unauthorised alteration, disclosure or destruction of data and personal information.

We restrict access to personal information to employees, contractors and agents in order to operate, develop or improve our services.

USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION

We use information held about you in the following ways:

To ensure that content from our website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer  
To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us, or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes  
To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us  
To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so  
To notify you about changes to our service  
We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by email.

If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by e-mail with information about our services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you.

If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data (the registration form).

DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets  
If JAFX Ltd or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets  
If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms & Conditions and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of JAFX Ltd , our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction  
YOUR RIGHTS

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at support@jafx.com.

Our Website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

CONTACT

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to support@jafx.com

Full Cookie Policy  
What are cookies?

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the website. Most web browsers allow some control of cookies through browser settings.

How we use cookies

When you use our website we may analyse basic information about your activity within our website. This information will provide us with general information about the users of our website, providing us a better understanding of user requirements. We will not attempt to attribute such traffic information to anything that is personally identifiable. Additionally, information relating to the Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser and operating system may be observed.

Web Browser Cookies

If you don’t wish to accept our cookies you can modify your browser so that it notifies you when cookies are sent to it or you can refused cookies altogether. You can also delete cookies that have already been set. You can still continue to use our website but it means we won’t be able to use your visit to help us improve your experience. It also means the cookie policy will continue to be visible as it takes a cookie to remember that you don’t want to accept cookies.

How do I delete cookies?

JAFX Ltd will not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information about you. However, if you wish to restrict or block the cookies which are set by JAFX Ltd websites, or indeed any other website, you can do this through your browser settings. The Help function within your browser should tell you how. Alternatively, you may wish to visit www.aboutcookies.org which contains information of how to do this on a wide variety of desktop browsers.
